energymuse.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy

Energy Muse Jewelry Inc. respects your right to privacy and is committed to protecting our customers’ Personal Information (defined below).  This Privacy Policy summarizes the following practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure practices for www.energymuse.com

  1. What information does Energy Muse collect from you, how do we collect information from you and how do we use it?
  2. With whom do we share your information?
  3. How can you update, correct or delete your personally identifiable information?
  4. What are your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?
  5. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
  6. Use of “cookies.”
  7. Contacting Energy Muse about privacy questions or concerns.
  8. Changes to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website owned and/or operated by or on behalf of any third party, even if we provide a link to such website on our Website. Capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meanings given such terms in the Energy Muse’s Terms and Conditions of Use.

When we refer to “Energy Muse,” “we,” “us” or “our,” we mean Energy Muse Jewelry Inc or the specific division, subsidiary, affiliate or Agent (defined below) that operates this Website, provides its content or processes information received through it, each as appropriate and applicable. 

When we refer to “you” or “your,” we mean the person accessing this website. If the person accessing this Website acts on behalf of, or for the purposes of, another person, including a business or other organization, “you” or “your” also means that other person, including a business organization. 

We created this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect Personal Information, what types of Personal Information we collect, how we use it, the steps we take to safeguard it, and the choices you have regarding how it may be used and disclosed. This Privacy Policy addresses some types of information, including Personal Information, means of collecting such information, and uses of such information that may not presently apply to one or more of the Websites. We are nevertheless advising you about these matters because we want to maintain flexibility in offering additional features without having to revisit this Privacy Policy every time we revise the Websites or offer new functions. No description of any type of information, means of collecting information, including Personal Information, or use of such information will obligate us to collect any particular information, make any particular use of any such information, or offer any particular functionality. 

In order to operate the Website and provide you with information, products and services that may be requested by or of interest to you, we may also collect and retain Personal Information. “Personal Information” refers to information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, such as information you provide on our forms, surveys, applications or similar online fields. Examples of Personal Information may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, Social Security number, date of birth or financial information (e.g., passwords, bank and other financial institution account numbers and billing address) and demographic information (e.g., zip code, hometown, gender, financial transaction history information and age. 

By submitting your Personal Information through our Website, you will be considered to have given your permission and consent for the collection, use, retention and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Use of our Website and Energy Muse’s services is strictly limited to persons who are of legal age in the jurisdictions in which they reside. You must be at least eighteen (18) years of age to use our Website and Energy Muse’s services. Energy Muse will not knowingly accept any information from an individual under the age of thirteen (13) years. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), any information that Energy Muse may receive from any individual who is reasonably believed to be under the age of thirteen (13) years will be deleted. If you are under the age of thirteen (13) years, please do not provide any Personal Information through the Website. If you are under the age of thirteen (13) years and have already provided Personal Information through the Website, please have your parent or guardian contact us immediately using the information below so that we can remove such Personal Information from our files. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website or offline point of contact between us and you. This Privacy Policy does not cover information, including Personal Information, we collect by means other than the Website. If you have any questions about how we use information, including Personal Information, collected by means other than the Websites, you should inquire at or before the time you give such information to us. 

Energy Muse reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of the terms, in whole or in part, of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically, as we may update it from time to time. Each time you visit any of the Websites or provide us with information, including Personal Information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy as in effect at that time. 

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE GATHER?

When you visit this Website, you may provide Energy Muse with two types of information: Personal Information you knowingly and voluntarily choose to disclose, and information that we automatically collect as you browse this Website. We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing, affiliate marketing and shipping. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Energy Muse and its affiliates.

The web servers that serve the Website may gather certain navigational information about where visitors go on our Website and information about the technical efficiencies of our Website and services. In the process of gathering navigational information, anonymous information may be collected which will provide information regarding a visitor’s use of our Website. Anonymous information means information that does not directly or indirectly identify, and cannot reasonably be used to identify, a particular individual. Examples of anonymous information may include information about your Internet browser, domain type, service provider and IP address information collected through tracking technologies (see “How We May Collect Your Information,” below, for additional information regarding our use of tracking technologies) and aggregated or de-identified data. We may also collect location information, which means information that may be collected by certain mobile applications and that identifies your physical location. This information may be collected from your mobile device’s location-aware features when you request certain services that are dependent on your physical location.

#### How We May Collect Your Information:

  * Information Collected and Stored Automatically
  * Your IP Address
  * Like most e-commerce websites, each time you visit any Website, we may automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the Websites for you and to diagnose potential issues with our Website, we may use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. We may also supplement this information with Website traffic information that is collected automatically when you visit our Website, and with information acquired from our joint marketing partners, third parties and our affiliated companies.

#### Cookies

We may use a browser feature known as a “cookie.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the computer that runs an Internet browser and is commonly used to store information about a consumer’s online activities, including information such as the content or advertisements that a consumer views or the pages a consumer visits within a particular website. It can contain information about you, your computer, your browser, your session, the websites you visit and other information about you or others who use, or have used, the computer or browser you use to access the Internet. Cookies are used for record-keeping purposes: the stored information can be retrieved by our website server when you return to the website. This allows us to personalize or regulate the use of this Website, and it also permits us to automate the access and data entry functions of this Website (e.g., login information), and to tailor the appearance or presentation of this Website to your preferences or interests. The cookies we use, if any, are not linked to any Personal Information while using this Website unless you have given us permission to link Personal Information to one or more cookies. Please note that you give us that permission any time you register on this Website, use or conduct a transaction through this Website, or identify yourself or the computer you are using through this Website. 

We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our Website is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our Website. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our Website). We may also use cookies to offer you or inform you of products, programs or services and targeted advertising. You can opt to have your browser reject cookies. 

Most or all browsers permit you to disable or reject cookies. You can do this by adjusting your preferences in the browser. [Energy Muse does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals.] Accordingly, your selection of the “Do Not Track” option provided by your browser may not have any effect on our analytics or tracking tools. Use the “Help” feature of your browser to obtain more information about refusing cookies. If you set the browser you use to reject cookies, you may not be able to access the Websites or use the full functionality of the Website, or it may take additional time to utilize such functionality. If you opt to reject cookies, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our Website. Your continued use of our Website reflects your consent to allow additional cookies to be placed on your computer to help you navigate the Website.

You should also know that companies that advertise on our Website (and their agents), and one or more of the organizations with which we do business, or to which we provide links from the Website, might use their own cookies. This Privacy Policy does not cover how these organizations use their cookies. We have no control over such organizations’ uses of cookies, and you should review the privacy policies of such organizations to determine the uses such organizations make of cookies. 

#### Flash Cookies

We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences and to assist with online authentication by allowing us to recognize you and your device when you return to the Website. This permits us to display content based upon what you view on our Website to personalize your use of our services. Our Agents (defined below) also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data they collect, as well as how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your device or browser will not remove Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies, you will not have access to many features that make your user experience more efficient.

#### Pixel Tags, Web Beacons, Clear GIF’s and Other Similar Technologies

These are typically small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the Website, our Applications or certain e-mail communications. They may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use these technologies to compile information we collect about you.

#### Clickstream Data

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a website’s server. Clickstream data can identify the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the website from which you linked to the Website. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-Personal Information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of the Website, how visitors navigate throughout the Website and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors.

#### Log Files

We or our hosting provider may collect traffic information from visitors for statistical analysis and Website improvement. When you access the Websites, we or our hosting provider may collect information about your visit in a log file on a server. Log file information may include, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We or our hosting provider use this information to analyze trends, administer sites, track users’ movements in the aggregate, and gather demographic information for aggregate use. We and/or our hosting provider may review this information to better understand overall trends and to determine what kinds of content are popular with and useful to users.

#### Information Other Websites Collect from You

Our Website may contain links to other websites operated by other parties whose practices may be different than ours. When you click on such links and visit such other websites, you need to be aware that we may not control such other websites or such other websites’ business practices, and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to such other websites. Consequently, the operators of such other websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the Website. You should check the other sites’ privacy notices because we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them. We encourage you to review other websites’ privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for the actions of the operators of such websites, or their use of your information.

#### Information You Voluntarily Submit. 

We collect and store any information you enter on this Website or provide to Energy Muse in other contacts we have with you. Information is collected from visitors to this Website, including in the areas described below, as applicable. During the online ordering process, you can review, change or delete personally identifiable information that you have submitted. You may change any of your personally identifiable information in your account online at any time. You may request to have the information on your account deleted or removed, although you cannot delete information associated with past purchases.

Contact Information \- If you contact Energy Muse’s customer service representatives by telephone, e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with this Website, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. If you contact Energy Muse through our feedback area or by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name and e-mail address in order to send you a reply. If other users or third parties send Energy Muse correspondence about your activities or purchases on this Website, we may keep the information in a file specific to you. 

Shopping and Website Registration \- We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to report non-personally identifiable information to any of our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on this Website. We collect information from visitors to this Website regarding the URLs they came from, their IP addresses, domain types, the browser type used to come to this Website, the country, state and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages of this Website that visitors viewed during their visit, and any search terms entered on this Website.

Placing Orders \- When you order from Energy Muse, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address and a password. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. 

Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contains. These changes will be automatically kept for future use.

[Gift Certificates \- If you purchase a gift certificate from this Website, you will give Energy Muse the recipient’s name, email address and phone number for the recipient. The recipient information you give Energy Muse will only be used to send the gift certificate and for no other purpose.] 

Online Surveys \- In order to improve our services to you, we sometimes ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an independent third party. Individual survey answers are confidential, although non-personally identifiable information is collected and disclosed to third parties. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.

Newsletters – From time to time, we may provide free newsletters and promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. We may periodically send you newsletters and e-mails listing current specials and deals. To stop receiving our newsletter, follow the instructions given in said newsletter.

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use your Personal Information to communicate with you if and when necessary in connection with your use of this Website, to respond to your questions, or to send you material and information you request. We may also use your Personal Information to:

  * Personalize your Website experience and allow Energy Muse to deliver the type of content and product information in which you are most interested;
  * Process your orders for products and services;
  * Respond to any questions you may have;
  * Respond directly to you for clarification of your questions;
  * Process your request for materials or information;
  * Register you for an event, contest or sweepstakes, if you request it;
  * Provide you with e-mail messages and other information regarding upcoming events, new products or services and general information about our products and services and those of our select business partners. You may elect not to receive these communications, either when you initially register at this Website, or at any time thereafter. See the section of this Privacy Policy called “CHOICE/OPT OUT”.

We may also use collected information in order to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer this Website.

#### E-mail Address

We may use your e-mail address to provide customer service information or answer your questions and requests. We may also occasionally send you our e-mail updates, notifications or other information about our products and services or about the products and services of our affiliated companies. We may share your e-mail address with our affiliated companies to enable them to send you e mails directly regarding their products and services, sales and other promotions. We include information in each commercial e mail that allows you to opt out of receiving future communications. 

#### Telephone Contact

If you provide us with your phone number, you may receive telephone contact from us for customer service purposes, and to assist us in responding to your requests and questions. We may retain this information for business and marketing purposes and to help us with future requests from you. We may occasionally use your phone number to contact you with updates or other promotional information about our products and services or those of our affiliated companies in which you may be interested. We may also make your Personal Information available to our affiliated companies to enable them to contact you directly with their promotional information, such as information about their products and services, sales and other promotions. 

#### Financial Information

By engaging in any kind of activity on the Website that uses financial information, you consent to our using your financial information, or providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary, to process your transactions. These third parties may include banking institutions used to process these transactions. Any of these various third parties are authorized to use your financial information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control. 

#### Demographic Information

We may use demographic information to tailor the Websites and communications to the interests of our users. We may share anonymous, aggregated (grouped) demographic information with our advertisers and other third parties so that they can tailor their advertisements and communications to the appropriate audience. If you consent to have us share, or we are otherwise allowed to share, your Personal Information, as described herein, then the demographic information that we provide to third parties may be linked to your Personal Information so that such third parties will be able to know about your demographic information on a non-anonymous basis.

We also may use all information we collect to analyze statistical use patterns and demographic data (basically, where our visitors come from and what demographic characteristics they have) and to improve this Website to better serve our customers. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We may also prepare and keep statistical records and other data about you and other users of this Website, but we do so in a way that does not identify you or any other user personally. We may hire third parties to help Energy Muse collect and analyze such data, and we may share such statistical data with third parties. Again, such statistical data will not specifically identify you or any other user. We use this information to help us make this Website more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of visitors to this Website, what part(s) of this Website they are interested in, how long they use this Website, and the types of technology our visitors use.

## DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHERS.

The personally identifiable information collected by Energy Muse is used only for the limited purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including for processing orders for products and services, for keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving this Website and its performance, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you.

We will need to use and disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties to charge your credit card, fill your order, deliver your order, provide customer service, provide you with credit and deliver promotional e-mails to you from Energy Muse. In connection with these transactions, we collect data necessary to complete the transaction that is furnished by you. This information may be furnished to a third party in order to facilitate the transaction. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for your order. Similarly, we must release your address information to the delivery provider to deliver products that you ordered from Energy Muse. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for fraud/credit risk purposes.

We may also provide your Personal Information and other information that you have provided to us through the Website to other companies (“Agents”) that provide services to help us with our business activities such as to host or maintain our Website; for data processing services; to provide website or data security; to provide operational, analytical or reporting services; or to provide technical support. In connection with providing those services to Energy Muse, an Agent may have access to your Personal Information. Such Agents will be contractually obligated to treat such Personal Information as private and confidential and not used for any purpose other than as Energy Muse authorizes, and not disclosed by the Agents to any third party.

Energy Muse may disclose your Personal Information when required by subpoena, court order or other legal process, or if it has a good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with any applicable federal, state or local law or regulation, (b) assist government enforcement agencies, (c) investigate, prevent or take action in connection with suspected or actual illegal activities, (d) investigate suspected or actual violations of Energy Muse’s rights, (e) protect the rights, property or safety of Energy Muse and its customers or employees, or others, (f) investigate and defend against any third-party claims brought against Energy Muse or (g) protect the security and integrity of our Website.

We consider the information that you provide to us to be a business asset of ours. Accordingly, Energy Muse may also disclose Personal Information and other information to a third party in connection with the sale, assignment or transfer of some or all of the assets of Energy Muse or its subsidiaries or affiliates or as the result of a change in control of Energy Muse, in which case we will require any such third party to treat any such Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any such third party to whom Energy Muse sells, assigns or transfers Energy Muse’s assets will have the right to use the Personal Information and other information that you have provided to us. 

We may also disclose personal, financial and other information that you have provided to us to our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other affiliated legal entities and businesses with whom we are under common corporate control. 

Please note that no attorney/client relationship exists between us, and therefore no communication between us, or information you provide to us or input via use of a Website, will be subject to any confidentiality obligation or privilege against disclosure.

Energy Muse reserves the full and unrestricted right to use and disclose anonymized information; aggregated information or publicly available information that has not been combined with nonpublic Personal Information for purposes including, but not limited to, Energy Muse’s internal use and research.

Except in the limited circumstances stated in this section, we do not sell, rent, license, trade or otherwise disclose the Personal Information of visitors to this Website to unaffiliated third parties.

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

There may be links on our Websites that direct users to third-party websites. If you follow any such links and you enroll in the respective services, your name and other requested information will be transferred to the operators of the respective third-party website. If you choose to use these third-party services, please review the third-party website’s terms of use and privacy policy prior to any transfer of your personal, or other, information. Energy Muse is not affiliated with such third-party websites, and you therefore acknowledge and agree that your use of such third-party websites is at your own risk, and Energy Muse will not be responsible for the operation of such third-party websites or your access and use thereof.

We may also contract with some third parties to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, as well as to provide offers and advertisements that may be of interest to you. Where authorized by us, these third parties may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile information about our website visitors.

#### Supplementation of Information

We may supplement the information we receive from you with other information we receive from third-party sources or clearinghouses. Thus, information we obtain through the Website may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than our Website, including both offline and online sources.

#### Information Ownership

We are the sole owner of the user information collected through the Websites. We may collect information from users at several different points on the Websites. 

#### Account and Password Security

You may receive a unique user name and password (“Access Codes”) upon completing a registration process for certain portions of the Website. It is your responsibility to safeguard and protect your Access Codes and to monitor use of these Access Codes for all purposes. You accept all responsibility for maintaining the security of your Access Codes and for all utilization of the Website via your Access Codes, with or without your knowledge or consent. You agree to (a) immediately notify Energy Muse of any unauthorized use of your Access Codes or any other breach of security; (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session; and (c) notify Energy Muse immediately if you have lost your Access Codes or wish to terminate your access or have these Access Codes changed.

## SECURITY

Energy Muse will take reasonable precautions to protect Personal Information provided to us through the Website from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Energy Muse has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure such Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary.

While Energy Muse strives to undertake reasonable and necessary efforts to secure Personal Information provided to us through the Website, even such security measures do not guarantee the security of all Personal Information, and Energy Muse cannot guarantee that the Personal Information it collects, uses and retains will be protected in all circumstances, including those beyond Energy Muse’s reasonable control. 

Particularly sensitive information may be encrypted. You can usually tell whether encryption is being used by noting the “locked” or other status indicator on the browser you are using. If the browser you are using does not indicate that the session is secure (e.g., by displaying a lock, a key or a similar icon), you should assume that the connection is not secure and that third parties will receive the information shared by you and us during that part of the session. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computer networks that may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and the country or jurisdiction in which these computer networks are located may not have privacy laws as protective as the laws in your country or jurisdiction.

Because we are committed to your privacy, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the Personal Information we collect online. When you place an order or access your Personal Information on this Website, we offer the use of a secure server. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to Energy Muse or from us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. In the event of an actual or suspected security breach, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of such.

#### International Users

If you are visiting the Website from outside of the United States, your connection may be made through and to servers located in the United States, your registration, entries and orders placed through the Website may be fully processed in and from the United States, and all information you provide may be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using the Websites, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the United States and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This Privacy Policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of Illinois and the United States, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the courts the United States in the State of Illinois.

#### Notice Regarding Unauthorized Access or Disclosure of Personal Information

For the purposes of any applicable law regarding notification of persons whose Personal Information was, or is reasonably believed to have been, acquired by an unauthorized person, any required notification may, where permitted by law, be made by the use of e-mail, telephone, fax or mail (including a notice printed in an available area of a bill or statement) or by posting a notice on the Website. The specific means used is up to us, and we will use our best judgment based on the circumstances. Where any notice is to be sent to a specific address or number (such as an e-mail address, physical address, telephone number, etc.), we will use the latest available address in our records. YOU AGREE TO THIS MEANS OF NOTIFICATION.

#### Website and Service Updates

We may send to you updates and service announcements about our Websites, but you may not un-subscribe or opt not to receive such announcements because such announcements contain important information about the products and services offered through the relevant Website(s). 

#### Correcting or Updating Personal Information

If your Personal Information changes or if you have reason to believe that your Personal Information as we maintain it is incorrect and you are unable to change your Personal Information by logging into your account, you may contact us at info@energymuse.com, and we shall attempt to accommodate all reasonable requests for such changes. Note that some information may be changed only by contacting the administrator of the Website.

## CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY

By using this Website, you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. We indicate the date of the current Privacy Policy above, so you know when it was last updated. Continued use of this Website after any such revision or modification constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy as so revised or modified. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on one or more Websites and/or other places we deem appropriate. BY USING THE SITE(S), YOU AGREE TO THIS CHANGE PROCEDURE. You have the opportunity to review this Privacy Policy each time you use this Website so that you are aware of any modifications made to these policies. This Privacy Policy supersedes all previous versions hereof.

## CHOICE/OPT OUT

This Website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Energy Muse at the point at which we request information about the visitor. You have the option of reviewing or removing your information from our database and to no longer receive communication from us. If you request that your account information be deleted from our database, we may maintain information about individual sales transactions for the purpose of record keeping and servicing.

We recommend that users who no longer wish to receive promotional materials or have their information provided to third parties log into their accounts and modify their account settings, as users may have chosen to receive promotional materials in the account registration process. If you are still receiving promotional materials 30 days after modifying your account settings, you may contact us directly using the information below to opt out of receiving such communications or having information shared. Our compliance with such requests may involve batch processing and other processes that take 30 days or longer. If you opt not to receive such communications or to allow us to share your information and then you give your Personal Information to us again by using the Website or under other circumstances that permit us to use your information, we will regard your opt-out as having been rescinded. Also, please note that users may not necessarily opt out of receiving all communications from us or opt out of sharing certain information with third parties, as specified as being necessary in various portions of this Privacy Policy.

You may additionally opt out of receiving e mail communications by using the opt-out instructions included in an e mail you may receive from us. 

Please note that changing or deleting your information through the Websites, or otherwise opting out of receipt of e mail communications from us and third parties, will only change or delete the data in our database for purposes of transacting future business on or relating to the Websites and for managing future communications from us and third parties. These changes and deletions will not change or delete information collected or submitted pursuant to the Customer Agreement, or information already collected as part of a product or service purchase in our transactions database which may be shared with our third-party service providers regardless of your email preferences.

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to make any changes you request. Many such changes may be accomplished using batch processing (i.e., collecting a number of similar change requests and making all such changes at once), so the changes may not be immediately effective. If you require an immediate change to your Personal Information and are unable to make such a change using the available Website resources, please contact us.

You can contact us via e-mail at info@energymuse.com or by mail at the postal address shown below.

Please note that due to e-mail production schedules, you may also receive an e-mail message from Energy Muse after you have provided your opt-out notice. Because we plan our mailings in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications, please contact us again, and we will make every effort to correct the situation. We apologize for any inconvenience.

## QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY.

If you have questions about this Website or Energy Muse’s Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at info@energymuse.com. You can also contact us by mail at the following postal address:

Energy Muse Jewelry, Inc.  
2301 West 205th Street #103103  
Torrance, CA 90501

Copyright © 2018 Energy Muse Jewelry Inc. All Rights Reserved.
